

GERSON TIONGSON

SHS INSCTRUCTOR | WEB DESIGN | WEB DEVELOPMENT

Motivated ICT senior high school instructor, freelancer, web designer and developer with experience creating custom websites through HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and Wordpress. Currently taking a full stack development training to expand my knowledge and experiences in web development.



Address

Mobile



Email

3

Website

Banicain, Olongapo City, Zambales, Philippines

+639956445556 +639394857179 gerson.tiongson.12314@gmail.com tiongsongerson@gmail.com

gerson-tiongson.vercel.app

EDUCATION

BS COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2013-2019

President Ramon Magsaysay State University Iba, Zambales

BS COMPUTER SCIENCE

2011-2012

Gordon College Olongapo City, Zambales

WORK EXPERIENCES

INSTRUCTOR

OCT2019 - PRESENT

Asian Institute of Computer Studies Olongapo City, Zambales

ICT Instructor for almost 2 years, teaching computer related subjects such as Java Programming, Phyton, VB.net etc.

FREELANCER

2017 - PRESENT

Upwork

Freelancer at Upwork for over a couple of years doing graphic design, administrative task, etc.

DATA ANALYST/ENCODER

MAR2012 - AUG2013

SourceHov

Subic Bay Freeport Zone, Zambales

Analyzing errors and correcting the data in an online forms that company provided using the company web applications

OTHER EXPERIENCES

OJT - IT

AUG-SEP 2017

BURSTTECH CALL CENTER
Olongapo City, Zambales

OJT - GRAPHIC DESIGN

APR-SEP 2018

Morefun.ph

Subic Bay Freeport Zone, Zambales

SKILLS

















TRAININGS & CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Development Training Present
Web Developer Bootcamp 2020 -Udemy

HTML5 - Udemy 2021 CSS3 - Udemy 2021 jQuery - Udemy 2021

LINKS

github.com/Zeras12314



gersteps

fb.com/ZerasHyperion



Gerson#6317

Be behance.net/gerson12314